# Kinzey Rahardja

kinzeyrahardja1@gmail.com | 0406 212 889

# Computer Science Penultimate Student

## **SUMMARY**

Passionate for programming and a committed penultimate student looking for a role in front-end web development creating customer tailored products. I'm a motivated and proactive learner with a strong mindset for personal growth and a desire to absorb opportunities, skills and experiences. With strong interpersonal and collaborative skills, I can work effectively in a team to learn from others, compromise when necessary, or take leadership when needed. I plan to develop into a senior front-end developer over the next six years.

### **EDUCATION**

## Bachelor of Computer Science (Security Engineering) | UNSW

2019 - 2023 Term 1

- Started from a two year background in Mechatronics Engineering before pursuing Computer Science in my third year.
- WAM: 82.6 (Term 3 2021)
- Achievements: Finalist MAC x Hack Sprint Hackathon: Connect Cafe (2021) [Flask, Pytest, React, Figma], Newbie CTF Comp with SecSoc UNSW (2021), Highly commended in Dean's Honours List in School of Mechanical Engineering (2019)
- Extracurricular: Weekly Perry Park Volleyball Division 3 (2022), X-point Weekly Rockdale Men's Tennis Team (2020-2021), Campus Bible Study (Small Groups, Core Training, Indonesian Bible Study), St George's Anglican Youth Group Leader
- Additional self-education on Udemy: The Complete Web Developer 2022: Zero to Mastery, The Complete SQL Bootcamp 2022:
  Zero to Hero

#### Sydney Boys High School

2013 - 2018 | 98.8 ATAR

- Awards: High Plaque for high level participation in school life (2018), Merit List (top 20% overall academic grade) (2016 2018),
  Most Efficient Cadet in SHCU for exemplary behaviour (2017), NCSS Grok Programming Intermediate Course perfect score (2016),
  High Distinction for Australian Computational Thinking Competition (2016)
- Extracurricular: Army Cadets Unit (2015 2017), 2nd Grade Team Captain (2018), Fencing First Grade Sabre Team Captain (2017), 2nd Grade Tennis (2018), 3rd Grade Tennis Team (2016 2017), 2nd place in AAGPS 2nd Grade Tennis Premiership (2017), Team Captain for A Team (2013 2015)
- Additional self-projects: Tetris [Pygame + Python] (2016), Minesweeper [Pygame + Python] (2016)

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### Schindler Lifts Australia | Intern (Programming and Mechanical)

June 2021 - Current

The Schindler Group is a Swiss multinational company which manufactures escalators, moving walkways, and elevators worldwide



- Developed a Reliability Metrics Tool App in Microsoft Access through a combination of SQL and VBA.
  - The aim: to have a centralised front-end that produces meaningful reliability metrics and graphs for non-technical Sales and Technical managers across Schindler Australia. Works off a single back-end database of multiple tables that has a developed GUI to allow for easy importing of several data sources from Schindler's SAP Software.
  - Used Lucid Chart for documentation on the query hierarchy. Used One Note and Microsoft Teams for organisation of project requirements, testing, validation, and change logs. Had weekly meetings with Project Manager on latest version of the App.
- Developed a <u>Technician Compliance Excel Interface</u> for Schindler's non-technical national EHS Manager.
  - Opens multiple excel data dumps of safety courses completed to produce an overview, per state, of each Technician. Used buttons and visual graphics to automate the process.
  - Included a non-technical visual output log of error-causing entries to allow for Manager to resolve.
- Helped in smaller settings on various Excel VBA and Microsoft Access Database problems for work colleagues.
- Did mechanical research to design a scissor lift to problem solve for technicians injuring their lower spine from lifting the control box out of escalator pit. Provided technical analysis and feasibility report.

#### Phoenix Education | Tutor

Oct 2019 - 2021

Group class teacher for Year 12 students (30 employees)

- Tutored 10+ preliminary and HSC students, specialising in Physics, Engineering Mechanics and 3U Maths.
- · Prepared resources for students outside of working hours, including class content, homework and quizzes.
- Developed interpersonal and communication skills for lessons to be customised to the needs of individual students.
- My strength is to understand complex concepts to present in a simple but accurate manner.

#### SKILLS

#### **Technical**

- Web Devlopment tools: NPM, React [Webpack], GitHub/Gitlab
- Programming languages: HTML CSS JS: React JS [2021-2022], Python [2016, 2021-2022], VBA [2021-2022],
  Bricx for Lego Mindstorms [2016-2018], C and C++ [2019-2020], MATLAB [2020], PostgreSQL [2020].
- Numerical and computing packages: Solidworks and Maple.
- Languages: Fluent in English and Indonesian, developing in Mandarin.
- Telecommunication skills: Zoom, Slack, Microsoft Teams, Google Meet.

#### Soft

- Strong perseverance and problem solving developed through a life within competitive sport settings
- History of strong written, verbal and intercultural communication and listening skills demonstrated through team sports, managing group projects and teaching
- Ability to accept and apply feedback with a strong desire to learn

# **REFERRALS**

Schindler Metrics Tool Project Manager: Thomas White | 0447 951 552
 Schindler Supervisor and Technical Director: Geof Devitt | 0417 513 476